const store = [
    {
      question: 'What’s the name of Arya Stark’s sword?',
      answers: [
        'Longclaw', // 0
        'Oathkeeper', // 1
        'Needle', // 2
        'Ice', // 3
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Needle'
    },

    {
      question: 'What does the word Khaleesi refer to?',
      answers: [
        'One of Daenerys Targaryen’s captured cities',
        'A title given to the wife of a Dothraki warlord',
        'All Men Must Die',
        'The name of the Night King',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'A title given to the wife of a Dothraki warlord',
    },

    {
      question: 'Who\'s family motto is "Winter is Coming"?',
      answers: [
        'House Stark',
        'House  Lannister',
        'House Tyrell',
        'House Targaryen',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'House Stark',
    },

    {
      question: 'Which character besides Jon Snow has also died and been resurrected by a Red Priest?',
      answers: [
        'Gendry Waters',
        'The Hound',
        'Beric Dondarrion',
        'Robb Stark',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Beric Dondarrion',
    },

    {
      question: 'Arya’s direwolf is named…?',
      answers: [
        'Visenya',
        'Nymeria',
        'Aemon',
        'Viserion',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Nymeria',
    },

    {
      question: 'What is The Tyrell ancestral home?',
      answers: [
        'Winterfell',
        'Highgarden',
        'The Vale',
        'Stormlands'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Highgarden',
    },

    {
      question: 'What did Tyrion Lannister murder his father, Tywin, with?',
      answers: [
        'A dagger',
        'A crossbow',
        'Poisoned wine',
        'He strangled him with a necklace'
      ],
      correctAnswer:'A crossbow',
    },

    {
      question: 'Aside from Valyrian Steel, what else can kill White Walkers?',
      answers: [
        'A Raven',
        'Greyscale',
        'Ice',
        'Dragon glass'
      ],
      correctAnswer:'Dragon glass',
    },

    {
      question: 'Which king did Jamie Lannister slay to earn his “Kingslayer” nickname?',
      answers: [
        'King Robert Baratheon',
        'King Aegon I Targaryen',
        'King Aerys II Targaryen',
        'King Joffrey Baratheon',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'King Aerys II Targaryen',
    },

    {
      question: 'Who are Jon Snow\'s Real Parents?',
      answers: [
        'Wylla and Eddard Stark',
        'Elia Martell and Viserys Targaryen', 'Lyanna Stark and Rhaegar Targaryen', 'Cersie Lannister and Robert Baratheon'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Lyanna Stark and Rhaegar Targaryen',
    }
];
